[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
When there's a trade off between precision and recall, it's important for
عندما يكون هناك نوعًا من الارتباط بين الدقة والاستدعاء، فمن المهم
us to look at the two extremes.
أن ننظر إلى الطرفين.
What does it mean to have a classifier that's extremely precise?
ماذا يعني أن يكون هناك مصنف دقيق للغاية؟
And what does it mean to have a classifier that's extremely high recall?
وماذا يعني وجود مصنف يمكن استدعائه بشكل سريع للغاية؟
And how the two can go against each other sometimes.
كيف يمكن للطرفين أن يتعارضا مع بعضهما في بعض الأحيان.
First, let's think about what I call an optimistic classifier.
أولًا دعونا نفكر فيما أسميه بالمصنف المتفائل.
You might know some of these optimists in your life.
قد تعرف بعض المتفائلين في حياتك.
They think everything is good.
فهم يعتقدون أن كل شيء بخير.
How's it going?
كيف تسير الأمور؟
Good. Even if bad stuff is happening,
حتى عند حدوث بعض الأمور السيئة،
they say good.
يقولون هذا جيد.
Those folks say that all possible experiences are good, so
هؤلاء الأشخاص يقولون إن كل الخبرات المتاحة هي أمر جيد،
they're optimists.
ولذا، فإنهم متفائلين.
That means that pretty much every input, every sentence,
وهذا يعني أن كل إدخال وكل جملة،
is labeled as positive, very few get labeled as negative.
يتم تصنيفها كشيء إيجابي، وقليل جدًا منها ما يتم تصنيفه سلبيًا.
It's extremely likely that all the truly positive data points get labeled as good.
وبالتالي، فمن المرجح للغاية أن جميع نقاط البيانات الإيجابية يتم تصنيفها كشيء جيد.
What does that mean?
ما معنى ذلك؟
That means that I have perfect recall,
يعني ذلك أن لدي استدعاء مثالي،
because I recall all those positive data points.
لأنه يمكنني استدعاء جميع نقاط البيانات الإيجابية هذه.
Good.
جيد.
But I might not get
ولكن قد لا أحصل على
perfect precision because I put in a bunch of negatives into that bit.
الدقة المثالية، لأنني قد وضعت مجموعة من السلبيات في هذا الجزء.
How can we address that?
كيف يمكننا معالجة ذلك؟
We can have that pessimistic classifier,
يمكننا استخدام ذلك المصنف المتشائم،
you might have some friends like that where you try really hard,
قد يكون لديك أصدقاء على هذا النحو، حيث تحاول جاهدًا،
you do everything for them, you go out of your way, and everything sucks.
وتقوم بكل شيء من أجلهم، وتبذل أقصى جهدك، ولكن في النهاية يصبح كل شيء مزريًا.
Every single experience that you have is really bad.
كل تجربة تخوضها هي سيئة حقًا.
There's very, very, very, very, few things that they say are good.
حيث إن هناك أشياء قليلة للغاية التي من الممكن أن يقولوا إنها جيدة.
And when they are there very likely to be good but everything else they say is bad,
عندما يكون من المرجح أن تصبح كل الأمور جيدة، ولكن كل الأشياء الأخرى تخبرك بأن الأمر سيئ،
so everything else in the world is very hard, equals -1.
لذا، فإذا كل شيء صعب من حولك يساوي القيمة -1 هو شيء متشائم،
Pessimist means that you're going to miss out on many good things in life.
فإن ذلك يعني أنك ستفوت الكثير من الأمور الجيدة في الحياة.
The pessimists have high precision because the few things that was good tends to be
ولدى الأشخاص المتشائمون درجة عالية من الدقة، لأن الأشياء القليلة التي يرونها جيدة هي في الواقع جيدة،
good, but very, very, very low recall, they don't inspire great things in life.
ولكن لديهم استدعاء منخفض للغاية، حيث أنهم لا يتأثرون بالأمور الجيدة في الحياة.
It turns out there is a spectrum between a high precision low recall model and
وقد اتضح أن هناك منظورًا بين نموذج الدقة العالية والاستدعاء المنخفض،
low precision high recall model, the pessimist and the optimist.
ونموذج الدقة المنخفضة والاستدعاء العالي، وهو ما يمثل التشاؤم والتفاؤل.
What we'd like to do is somehow balance between the two perspectives in the world
وما نود القيام به، هو تحقيق التوازن على نحوٍ ما بين المنظورين في العالم
to find something that's just right for us.
لإيجاد شيء مناسب تمامًا لنا.
So, balance between a pessimistic model and the optimistic model.
لذا، فالأمر متعلق بإيجاد التوازن بين النموذج المتشائم والنموذج المتفائل.
In particular, we want to find as many positive reviews or sentences as possible,
وعلى وجه الخصوص، فنحن نريد إيجاد أكبر عدد ممكن من الملاحظات أو الجمل الإيجابية،
as many of those as possible, with as few incorrect predictions as we can.
مع أقل عدد ممكن من التنبؤات غير الصحيحة.
So, that's the balance we're trying to strike in the case of our restaurant.
لذا، فهذا هو التوازن الذي نحاول إيجاده في حالة هذا المطعم لدينا.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]